(The Wack In the Future)
I'm not willing to, Doraemon
Isn't there a way to beat Jian
OK Since Nobita said so
Let me help you to revenge
Doraemon, bring out
the Air Ring
What's this?
Put it on your middle finger
and shout Pound
Pound
It's painful
Are you OK Doraemon
What's the matter
That's Air Ring
which can defeat the opponent
Powerful
If we have this one, Jian will...
If he beat me, I'll shoot him
Where's Jian
I'll teach him a lesson
Nobita, you asked anything
from Doraemon
Yeah
Great Nobita got the support
of Doraemon
Let me have a look what's it
I found him Jian
Jian, if you want to apologize,
you'd do it now
What did you say
You become bold suddenly
Don't you regret
What will I regret?
Great...
Pound Bomb
It flies
Impossible
The Air Ring will appear in the future
I don't care Doraemon
I must bring out the instrument
which will help me win
Use this one The lucid cloke
You can become a
lucid man and beat him
Although it's not above board
you needn't worry
Er, I'll go
Where's damn Jian
What a pain
There's a wall which couldn't be seen
Nobita, you went to the trap
Jian
This is an almighty
trap which can deflate
all big animals and tempt them in
Nobita, Dola A
Dream isn't frightening now
I've many good stuff
What'll we use this time
R's hedge
What's the use of it
Wow, it flies into the sky
I've a sense of unease
Something must happen to Nobita
Help me
Er? ls the sound just now
Nobita's?
I'm here, Doraemon
Nobita
Bad There're many future instrument
in Nobita's pocket
What
How could he get them
He could not have the time machine
I must take it back
It'll be bad if Jian uses it
Doraemon Help me
I found him
He's having a rest on the fixed cloud
I found a good thing
Many interesting things
can be taken out from this bag
That's...
Jian, where did you get it
This is mine
Stop there
Give it to me
No
Boring
What's this?
We'll know after using it
It's itch powder
It's very tickle
Do you know it's powerful
OK, take the stuff of
Doraemon's almighty pocket now
Doraemon Let me
get out Sorry to trouble you
Thank you, uncle
Brother Who used this stuff?
The rascal named Jian
let me see him
It's very heavy
What's the thing like a TV
Is it the switch here
Isn't it
Time Patrol Team contacts urgently
The headquarter
of 22nd Century Time Patrol Team
It's Jian !
I found it
We're searching it now He may escaped
to the past with the time machine
Please check different worlds now
This is the criminal's picture
You heard my secret
It's troublesome
I know you're the owner of the bag
You'll disappear if you know my secret
It's useless to shout
Dad! Mom!
I want have some gong cake
We caught up with it luckily
It's time patrol team
I was helped
Give the bag taken by this man
It's hard for me to pick it...
I'd get a part of it
Jian's too childish
You'd be grateful for you're saved
Give it to me
Or I'll ring the bells backward
Damn What's the matter
Was I dreaming before
It's painful~
(The love of machine)
You eat it so quickly
Girls surrounded me shouting
and they asked me to teach them
They're waiting for me I'll go now
I'll vapid
It's better as long as he's happy
Shizuka, is what you said true
I'm joking But he really apologized
Sorry to keep you waiting so long
Let me show you first
Then
Everybody
I bought a new PC machine
Come to my home to play
OK I'll go Me too
Well Let's go now
But...
Don't worry about me
I've something to do
Really It's a pity
Everybody, let's go
See you
And then you have groundnut yourself
You're so thirsty
It's kidding
But I know you're deeply hurt
It's good that girls applaud to you
But I was betrayed immediately
Good! I'll help him
to make an excellent girlfriend
You do your homework yourself
Well Don't be shy Come over
Let me introduce
He's Machine from the future world
I'm Machine Nice to meet you
Hello I'm... the... Hello
Get on well with each other you two
No way Little Tinkling
Will she make friends with me
Don't worry
That's my friend, Machine
She's adjusted, she'll like you
That...
Are you really want to be my friend
Sure
But my achievement isn't good
I've not sports neuro
I like your characters
You rank first among the men in Japan
It's the first time
that people said me like this
I think of one thing I'm good at
Look carefully
He'!
Cool
Beautiful
I'm thirsty
Wait a moment
Please drink it
It's too exaggerating
Ah It's homework
No, don't look at my note
Great
Not everyone can
make such unique mistake
Are you praising me
But teacher will get angry with me
Let me write the answer that he likes
Nobita
Go to help buy something
Tiresome...
It's Pity
How can you do that
Let me help you to buy
It's not good
I can't let you do anything
You're so tender
Dear, you can't love anyone but me
No, I promise you
I'm too glad
The strength is so big
Nice
None of us notice
such a beautiful girl
It's waste to give her to Nobita
It's painful
I'll not forgive anyone
if he dares to bully Nobita
You're powerful
I've 1 million horsepower
I'll protect you no matter who comes
Thank you
Nobita
Shizuka
Sorry I don't feel it's good
Will you pardon me
It doesn't matter
Bad
See you
Do you know what you'll suffer
if you love other girls
I see
Nobita, where were you just now
How come you bully Nobita
No, wait
Doraemon
What's up?
Bad
I can't bring robot any more
( Take out the cloud to play )
Keep off There's a shadow
Bad trick
Keep off
Why do you shout at the shy
That cloud
That cloud?
When the holiday's over
There's a muscle contest
I want to let it be in the sun
and make it black
but the cloud prevent the sunshine
Bad Keep off
Will the cloud move when blow
in this way
I see In fact it's
impossible to move
But at least I feel it's moving
No, the cloud can move
ls there any device to move it
The cloud controller
Is it that tool?
Look, the cloud comes out from the box
It's as the same as the cloud
in the sky
Which one do you want to move
Err... that one!
The lowest cloud
OK Since it's so...
Move the cloud below with it
Paint paint paint
OK! It moves!
Powerful machine
It's nothing
The boring sunshine appears again
It's hard to see a little cloud
and it's cool now
Mom's too poor
Can you make shadow only there
OK, it's simple
Separate it a little now
It'd be OK to move it here
Ah? Great! There's a shadow again!
Great
Can you change the shape
Sure, I can
Have a try?
I want to have a try
Make this cloud round
and cut a hole in the middle
It becomes a round cookie
Ah! It's alike
Nice
Very interesting
Enjoy it
It's a banana
It seems delicious
I don't know how about this one
It's an apple
It looks nice too
What'll we do next time
Change a difficult one
OK Grape
It's hard
What food shall we make next
Bad I ate too much
Let's make a plane!
What's you mark 80
Look, there's a strange cloud
How come it becomes so
It's incredible
I'm great surprised
Let's scare them
How about this one
Look, it's a dog
It becomes a cat
Really
I'm making a dog
OK, giraffe
It becomes a horse!
Really
They can't find it out
Well, it'll be found by a girl easily
It's a beautiful swan
It changes It's a duck
As if
impolite Their
understanding is too low
I'll do something to surprise them
How about it?
It's a snake
Shit
What shameful cloud
How dare you say that
I'm angry
OK, I'll get all the cloud together...
What's that
It seems like a genie
Boring It's terrible
How about it, is it fearful
How do you like it
Help me
It's Jian !
OK, let's play with him
What's the cloud
How dare you rebel me
You're over self-proud Let me
teach you a lesson Come over
You'll be surprised later
It's frightening this time
Do you want to fight
Ah!
How about it It's so this time
I saw nothing
Damn cloud
Set me free
Help
Do you know my power now
It's funny
Don't that money trick
Why it becomes dark suddenly
There's much cloud in the sky
Isn't it...
The cloud controller...
The switch isn't turned down really
It'll be bad
if you don't switch it down quickly
It's too hot
What it'll become
If it's burnt
The machine-WI short circuit
Forget the switch
It'll be so next time
sorry
( The Sellotape of Fact )
The sunny sky The white cloud
My heart is...
Popular star
Will you go to the TV station
Your joke is funny
Thank you
Jian's song is charming
When will the next concert begin
R's 'm preparation Lana
The idiot is easy to be whipped
The head's empty
I'll take another piece today
It smells nice
You're more beautiful than rose
Ah...
Shizuka Please accept the rose
Suneo Thank you
You're welcome
Beautiful flowers-'re for beauty
See you
Suneo's charming
Aunt You're hard-working
Suneo
What's up?
No, aunt looks younger than before
Boring Don't soothe me
No, it's true
Where...
Where will you go, Suneo
Yeah, I've to three lessons
before sunset
Three...!?
I'll be late, excuse me
Take care
Suneo's mother's really happy
to have such a son
To be compared with her...
Nobita, is your work finished
NO
You'd learn from Suneo
He won't stop learning until night
Why do you laugh
No, mom
Suneo didn't go to have class,
he always plays truant
He's not scolded by the teacher
for he's good at bootlicking
Nobita, you can't say that
Others will suspect your personality
What I said is true, mom
You don't believe me
It doesn't matter
He'll be found someday
It matters! I can't wait!
My personality's suspected
You're exaggerating
It's his right to do what he likes
But he can't get me involved
The sunny sky
Nobita, how do you like my new song
That's not important
I'm looking for Suneo
How dare you say that
No...
Don't be wordy!
You'd learn from Suneo
You speak of him again
Do you see Suneo, the bastard
Nobita, why do you said like that
Suneo's very tender and considerate
I want to marry such a man
after I grow up
What're you saying
You only take one flower... I see
I'll send you rose
I've never seen so beautiful roses
Then see you
Wait
Is it you who peep rose every day
No You mistake me
How do you understand the thing
just now
That's... that's...
You speak
What's up?
Is my friend a flower thief?
I... can't believe...
Aunt Please forgive him
I beg you for him
What a kind kid
What's up? Nobita
It's so Etc
What Suneo can't be forgiven
Put the sellotape of fact to him
The sellotape of fact?
Put the sellotape of fact
What he did secretly will come out
Don't worry
I'll persuade him
Sorry to trouble
Let me manage it
What? What?
It's only a rose You're so mean
I'll come to take rose everyday
How about it
I'm very angry
Ah
I'll not send it to you
without being paid
Write the work for me Don't refuse it
Shizuka Understand
I don't like Suneo
I'm so clumsy What's the matter
My good friend
Listen to my new song
I can't bear You always bootlick
What did you said just now
No, nothing
I only want to say I feel sick
to listen to you sing
This bastard
Damn
Help
The effect of the sellotape
is really curious
Thank you Doraemon
We know what Suneo is now
Great Nobita
Suneo What's the matter with you
Aunt, your wrinkle becomes more
Is it hard to raise a fool son
Ah...
Nobita
Have you finished your homework?
No
How come you become like this
Suneo told me truth just now
Mom's ashamed
It's only because
Nobita doesn't study carefully
It'll make trouble to tell the truth
( Fake Universe Man )
Really?
ls the UFO taken by Suneo and Jian?
We're murmuring in hear our heart
:UFO, fly over UFO, fly over
There's orange light appeared
before us suddenly
And then...etc.
UFO landed and a saucer man came out
Don't say that any more
This is secret
I force them to tell it out
They two met the sauce man and
talked with them
Really?
Sure
Another news is
there'll be UFO to land tonight
Let's peep it together
Impossible You like sleeping so much
Let's go
ls what you said true?
I'm sleepy It's so cold
Let's go back
You're too noisy, Doraemon
Let's murmur: UFO, fly over
UFO, fly over UFO, fly over
It's flimflam We're not playing ET
I can't stay with you
OK, you can go back now
A man without belief
will only prevent me
UFO, fly over UFO, fly over...
You were cheated
I heard he's standing here till the
early morning, and then he caught cold
You're too bad Nobita's too poor
But nobody will do that like him
Boring I'll go back
Shizuka
OK Let her alone
Let's take false photos
Let's cheat Nobita again
I've been feeling curious
from the beginning
Are you willing to do that, Nobita?
I'm angry that I'm an idiot
Of course
OK Since it's so...
Dangdang assembled UFO scene
Wow...
What a big toy
The children in the kindergarten
can play this in the future
There's one controlling sauce man
What's that
It's used in this way
I'm a sauce man, and I
come to the earth from far away
We can scare Jian with this
It becomes darker and darker
We'd go back now
Boob
We can take suitable pictures now
We can post our photos
to the magazine office
Maybe they'll be published
OK It's important
Don't forget to press the shutter
OK
Good I'll go now Go ahead
Take one photo
Who did it?
UFO!
Help
Please pardon me...
I'm from the 8th star of octopus
You made me great trouble
Please forgive us
We didn't know that
We won't play monkey tricks any longer
It's true
Look at their face
Hush It'll be heard
We come here
to talk with mankind
Nice
I agree
I want to meet your premier
Ask him here
Premier?
Do you mean the prime minister?
Impossible You like sleeping so much
What Don't you want to
hold a peaceful talk?
Do you want to have us as your enemy
I'll start the star war
Wait We'll look for him
Running while falling down
Is that premier
I'm sorry but would you come here now
A sauce man want to see you
Thank you
It's hung up
It's natural that
the opponent didn't respond
No way Let's look for him directly
Do you have his address
ls our money enough
Tell us where the premier is
It's not sweeping minister
but the prime minister
The star war will break out
if you don't hurry
OK I see
Wait
Great We'll be saved then
Please send the ambulance here
There're too strange kids here
There's no methods
Let's escape
Let's go to the remote island
You can't run away
Wait
You must bring the premier here
tomorrow
You must
Yeah
It'd be OK to scared
him to such degree
Are you willing to now
Do you have anything to discuss
with teacher? Say it
UFO landed
They said they'd look for the premier
Shut up. How dare
you fool your teacher
It's too much
( My birthday )
I've no interest to go to school
You always told me to work hard
When I want to study
mom tell me that again,
and I don't want to now
You'd believe me
Will you study yourself
Sure
OK, it's up to you
I'll go out to have a good time
Really
Nobita, you're so naughty
It's my shame
to teach such a child like you
It's egregious
It's really your mistake
But why you did like that
Maybe...
Right It must be so
I mustn't be a child of this family
I was picked outside
What're you saying
It's impossible
No It must be so
My real mom
where're you?
OK, let's confirm
with the time machine
till that day you were born
Right Why don't I notice that
in the past
What'll do if I was really picked
from outside
What're you saying Hurry
OK Move
till it's Aug, 7th of ten years ago
It arrives
My home of ten years ago
Everything is in order
There's no your paint
This was your dad's room before
There's nobody in
What's the matter
How was I born if there's no dad
It seems that I was really picked
Boring
It's a joke
It must be in the hospital
Where's it
It's dad
He really becomes ten years younger
who're you
How can you forget you're a kid
No, you aren't born
What's that?
No... that's not important
Where
My child is there
It's gone
Where's it on earth He's not here
I came back from work
after I received the call
Where's it earth He's not here
Is it in the hospital
Ah... right
who're you
From I saw you just now...
It's not important Go to the hospital
Your father's anxious
Wait Take us
Congratulations It's a boy
I'm full
No Thanks
That... this...
It's in tension
I'm too excited
I don't know what it's like
It must be like me
It's a very lively baby
I become a father now
It's very big it's like my wife
The baby's there
Excuse me
It's lively
Let me have a look
Is it me?
There's so much wrinkle like a monkey
How dare you say that
sorry
who're those children
They're always following me
I don't know
how their parents teach them
What'll the infant's name is
I've got one
Nobita
It means hero Is it fine
They'd asked the party
Don't do that You'll be scolded
Of course there's a good name
But the name contains my expect on him
I hope he'll be a good child
when he grow up
Of course he's an excellent kid
He'll be excellent in study
if he's like you
He'll be good at sports
Bad
He succeeded all your shortcomings
I'm very disappointed
Will he be a scholar or a politician...
It's nice to be an artist
Paint Sculpture Music
Everything is good
It's the best that he's considerate
Brave
Be strong...
Fearless Confident Honour
Handsome
That...
It's not good to expect too much
The child is quite ordinary
Really
No way Let's call it a deal
Does our child do violence to you?
You always said that from just now
I know you're the real one
They expect my future will be bright
Nobita, you'll damage your health
Go to bed
What's the matter with you
Why do you work so hard
Who knows how long he'll last
(Go to school by bow and arrow)
It'll be late
Huff)'
Jian What's wrong with you
Look, Nobita is washing his teeth
Nobita, you'll be late
if you don't hurry
And you'll be beaten by the teacher
It doesn't matter
Nobita It's time for meal
Yeah
What I know it's early
It's not good that we run like this
Walk slowly
You'll be late if you don't hurry
It doesn't matter
I won't be late today
Right Doraemon
Yeah Nobita
OK Be quick
OK OK
I'll go now
Nobita, the exit is here
I'll go through this way
Then let's go by the portage arrow
What kind of arrow shall we use
The yellow one
Catch me tightly
I see
It's faster than the dragonfly
It'll arrive at school
It'll land
The target's there!
It landed successfully
We're not late
Thank you Nobita
Seen far away,
the sky above the mountain...
Hey! You two come out!
You're late again
We thought time was enough...
Nobita has arrived
I can't believe
You're late, how dare you blame others
Stand in the corridor
I'm scolded this time...
it's all because of Nobita
OK, I'll beat him on the way home
Right
See you See you tomorrow
Wait
Nobita, will you come to my home
to play
OK
Doraemon,
put a blue target at Shizuka's home
Don't you go home
There's really no way
You change so fast
The target in Shizuka's is blue
So we'd use the blue arrow
Can we go there by arrow
Nobita's easy to to be in his glory
Damn He's not late for he used that
Let's take it back
when Doraemon's not here
It's OK
Shizuka Hug me tightly
Is it no problem
Nobita
Dangerous Go in hurry
It's caught It disappeared
Can it go anywhere
Yeah
It's OK as long as you put
the target in the destination
It arrived at my home
It arrived
It's really fast
I saw it fly in that direction
Don't let him run away
Shizuka, you bought battledore
I didn't use it
Shall we play lung
OK
Doraemon
Put the green target in the lung
It comes again?
I'm so tired...
It's Nobita
Damn Nobita flied again
Go!
Ah, my God
Bad
You're really good at making trouble
I run out of breath Nobita...
It's a red target
He'll go home by this one
OK We'll take it
to teach him a lesson
It fails I'm useless
That's no way
You played it only for a while
Let's call it day
You're right It's time to go home
How will you go home?
By red arrow
What'll we do with that target?
It's hard to be found here
Leave where it is
Bye-Bye We'll play it next time
See you See you tomorrow
It's strange It's not going home
It's curious
It's obviously put in the yard
Nobita, I've been waiting you
for a long time
What're you doing?
Turn the arrow out
No
It's green arrow
OK, let's have a try
Bring it over
Give it to me
No way Let's call it a deal
No way
Where's the green target?
It's put in the lung
It'll be bad if Jian uses it
Who put it there?
Suneo, what's the matter
It must be taken away by a dog
Help me
This is the retribution for
stealing others' things
Help me to get on
I'll be scold by mom
(With Mirror ads )
Morn What's up
Spook
Doraemon, are you playing tricks
What a pain
I didn't mean to scare you,
I was doing experiment just now
This is the telescope
The picture in it will appear
in other mirror
And the scope will expand
from my home to the whole area
If it's set to be auto
It'll reflect the man
who's looking into the mirror
But it'll also
reflect the same picture repeatedly
It's rare to see But
What's the use of it
It can be frightening just now at most
It's painful
You really wanted to scare others
just now
It's so Sorry
But Because I can't
find a good usage of it
it only occupies room,
and I want to destroy it
Wait It's interesting
Let me help think it over
I think it's useless
What's the usage of it on earth
Great
The yellow fox is swat king of mug-up
OK! We can put the ads on the mirror
Let's solicit ads to the small shops
Will you broadcast ads in the mirror
of this area
100 yuan per second
Then in one hour we can get...
24,000 yuan!
We'll earn much
Let's start tomorrow
I'm back
Welcome to go home
I'll go to solicit ads
The more the better
It's the age of ads
Your turnover will double
if you utilize the ads of our company
But people don't not often
look into mirror
No, it's not only mirrors
Windows, bright floor and loblolly
Everything which can reflect will mapped
Let me have a look
And we'll discuss it later
Our business is good,we don't need ads
We don't need There's another one
What're you doing?
Didn't you solicit one advertisement
Your thought's too old
Let make one free for one shop
as a special service
Right!
After they see the effect,
they'll do business with us
We can't do it with those
which run well
Let's look for it in the alley
OK!
We're looking for this kind of shop
It's so poor
and it may fall down anytime
It's a shop without customers
Nobody know it
Look, although our shop looks old
it's very clean
Really There's no dust
I have confidence on the products
Nice!
Why your business isn't good
After the street was
widened and beautiful
department stores were built up
nobody came here
It's troublesome
Let me manage it
We'll make ads for you
and many customers-'ll come here
Really
Wait and look
Make the effect best
And let people of
the whole area see it
1,2,3,4...
The steambread of Abala Cake Shop
had won championship 3 times
What? You made me cut my face!
The pellet there is big and cheap
And the Gong Cake there is 100 yuan
Please forgive us
I can't make up
if you don't disappear quickly
Abala Cake Shop Please do more favours
Nobita's a grey wolf
Will many clients really come
There's nobody coming although
I've been waiting for a long time
Let me go to have a look
Bad, it's bad
Everyone is angry now
They said they won't buy the cake
of Abala Cake Shop
So I didn't want to make ads at first
and I didn't ask you to do so
You made me trouble
You must compensate me
if there're no customers
The shop'll be bankrupt
It's our mistake Sorry
Never mind To tell you the truth
I'll just give it up
It's really our mistake
OK, don't cry any longer
If you like
you can have some cake in the shop
But...
Come onYou're welcome, help yourself
Thank you for your reception
You're welcome
You're the last customers
Really I'll take it now
Delicious
Can I eat so much
I've been longing to have cake
like this
The stuffing is nice
I'll ask my wife to buy it
Morn I want that one
Delicious
Great, really
It's nice!
Don't crush, please don't crush
Please queue
It's good that the
advertisement is successful
but it's too tied...
Some faces-'re round
Some faces-'re long
Some faces' re square
Some faces-'re triangular
Crying Angry Fawning and requesting
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round